DANIEL PRECIADO

CONTACT

+57 311 855 7304 danielpre30@outlook.com Git Hub <u>danielpre30</u>

Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Redux
- Node js
- Enzyme
- Sinon is
- Jest

PROFILE

Systems and Computer Engineer from Pontifical Bolivarian University, working as a frontend developer for the last 2 years and a half. With experience in Javascript, HTML, CSS, React and Node js.

Positive attitude of helping my colleagues and a willing to continuously grow professionally, that materializes in a constant exchange of ideas and knowledge within work teams. My goal is to collaborate on projects to continue training in the frontend area, delving into the basics of web development.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend Development Intern, Team International; Medellin – July 2019 - January 2020

After completing a training process with Team International in the Top Gun Lab program, I was chosen to intern at the company. During this period I was assigned responsibilities for:

- Front End software development
- Application maintenance
- Customer service

It was a period of professional and personal growth as this was my first professional experience.

Front End Developer, Team International; Medellin – February 2020 - Present

Once the internship process was over, I was hired as a junior developer, and later middle, to continue with the project I started during the internship. At this stage I was assigned additional tasks of:

- Code review
- Complex development tasks
- Mentoring for interns
- Demo presentation for clients

Freelance Front End Developer, Team International; Medellin – February 2021 - March 2021

During this period, I worked for a client that needed to improve the accessibility of a web application. From this experience I learned:

- Basics of accessibility in web pages
- ARIA attributes
- Some good development practices

EDUCATION

Systems and Computer Engineering

Pontifical Bolivarian University Medellín

2016 - 2020

Top Gun Lab Javascript

Team International Medellín 2019

Top Gun Lab React

Team International Medellín 2019

REFERENCES

David Villanueva Arévalo

Software Development Engineer | Team International +57 301 299 8291 david.villanueva.dev@gmail.com

Andres Betancur Rivillas

Software Development Engineer | Team International +57 311 734 2891 andres.betancur.dev@gmail.com

Sebastián Castaño Zuluaga

Operational Transformation Analyst | Seguros SURA +57 314 639 6641 scastano@sura.com.co